{
    "subject": "Deborah_Orr",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Will_Self",
    "human_readable": "Deborah Orr is married to Will Self.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9866513013839722,
            "question": "Is Will Self married to Deborah Orr?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9334888458251953,
            "question": "Are Deborah Orr and Will Self in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9019920229911804,
            "question": "Who is Deborah Orr married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8103176951408386,
            "question": "Do Deborah Orr and Will Self have any children together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7115790247917175,
            "question": "What is the name of Deborah Orr's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.633225679397583,
            "question": "What is the name of Deborah Orr's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5840258002281189,
            "question": "Who is Will Self?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32441312074661255,
            "question": "What do we know about Deborah Orr's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2970331013202667,
            "question": "What are some of Will Self's notable works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22514939308166504,
            "question": "Is Will Self famous for his writing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Deborah Orr is married to Will Self.",
            "html": "yago_30699_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Will Self's notable works?",
            "html": "yago_30699_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What do we know about Deborah Orr's profession?",
            "html": "yago_30699_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Will Self?",
            "html": "yago_30699_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30699_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the format you requested:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about Deborah Orr's marriage to Will Self, stating that they were married in 1997 and that she became stepmother to his children."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Deborah Orr is married to Will Self.\" The relevant details are found in several of the provided files, such as mentioning their marriage in 1997 and their roles as stepmother to each other\u2019s children."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}